generali.com 2017-08-04

# Privacy - Generali Group

Assicurazioni Generali S.p.A., acting as Data Controller, attaches utmost importance to confidentiality, protection and safety of information, particularly personal data concerning their customers and people who get in touch with the Company.

This section outlines the methods used to administer this site with regard to the processing of users' personal data. Pursuant to Art. 13 of Legislative Decree 196/2003 (Personal Data Protection Code), this information is also provided to subjects interacting with the services provided over the Internet by Assicurazioni Generali (Data Controller).

For this reason, Net surfers are invited to preliminarily visit the other sections hereto attached, which give an overview of Company guidelines on protection of personal data. Please consult the information note clicking on the present LINK to achieve all the information required by article 13 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003 (Personal Data Protection Code) concerning the processing of the internet users' personal data.

Information is provided for and applies to Assicurazioni Generali Web sites only. It is not applicable to any other Web site linked to the Generali site.

Surfers are required to provide personal data only if they want to get in contact with us or ask for advice. In such cases - totally voluntary - Surfers are required to read the Information as established by the Law and to provide only data strictly necessary to handle their requests.

In compliance with the existing privacy legislation, Assicurazioni Generali have adopted a specific policy, as described in the Assicurazioni Generali privacy policy section.

Surfers browsing our Web site are not required to provide any personal data. However, as the technology used by our Company stores data concerning tools employed by users, which help track the latter.

We are pleased to provide useful information on the methods of active and passive collection of information concerning subjects/means interacting with this Web site, as well as on the security measures taken by the Company.

While surfing a web site, it is technically possible to collect data even without a user's explicit registration to the service or without his active role. This type of collection is called “passive data collection”.  
The use of IP addresses, cookies and other session identifiers, Internet tags, and surfing data, including the possibility to exclude them and their implications, are shown below.

As regards the **passive data collection** :

  * the web site does not use IP address (Internet Protocol Addresses) to collect information. However, IP addresses are stored as surfing data;
  * it uses surfing data as aggregate data for statistical purposes only;
  * it uses its own and third parties' cookies and other session identifiers (technical and profiling). Technical cookies are used in order to make surfing possible or provide a service requested by the user only if strictly necessary, in compliance with the Legislative Decree no. 69/2012 and with the European legislation on personal data protection concerning the electronic communications services accessible to the public. For these purposes consent is not required. Third parties' profiling cookies are not used for statistical purposes - in anonymous form or not - in order to provide users a service in line with their preferences. The cookies for commercial profiling are not used. It is possible to disable the use of cookies depending on the browser, even though in this case surfing may not be equally easy;
  * it does not use Internet tags.  

As regards the **active data collection** \- if previewed - it is worth the following policy:

  * E-Mail: Data received by e-mails sent to the Web site are used to reply tequests only. This data are stored for statistical purposes only and to check whether there are any precedents.  
Names may be included in specific Mailing List only if expressly requested by Surfers wishing to receive certain documents (press releases, financial statements, etc.) on a periodical basis.
  * Registration: To access a number of services, Surfers are required to fill in a specific form. This information is used to reply to the sender's request and to provide requested services only.
  * Forums: specific conduct rules will be set out. Data will not be used for any other purpose.
